we-are-gamers.com 2012-10-12

# Privacy Notice : Gamers United Shop

At the time the order is placed we collect enough information to allow us to process your order, and contact you if necessary. All the information you provide is stored on our secure server.

When you choose to participate in a contest or a promotion, we may ask for your name, address, email address and phone number in order to administer the contest and notify the winners. Supplying this information is required to participate in the contest, by doing so you agree to allow us to email you. 

We do not collect information about your personal activity on the site, all ads are based on your location within the website. Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) does count the number of uniques and views per page, but is not associated with a particular user or user information. You will generally see ads for a particular product while within its own section, excepting the front page. We store your shipping information as it is part of your log-in information and required for shipment. 

We do not store information associated with your credit card, including your credit card number, expiration date, verification number on our web server. We do not use third party advertisers or contact lists. We do not use third party advertisers or contact lists. 

In addition to the information you provide when you use the Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) web site, we use technology to collect anonymous, non-personally identifiable information about your use of the site. 

**Information Disclosure**  
When you place an order with us, we do not share your information with any third parties. We do not sell or rent any of your personally identifiable information with anyone outside of Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/).

We may provide your information, as required by law or legal process or under circumstances we believe reasonably necessary to protect the personal safety of users of Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/), this site or the public.

 **Links to External Sites**  
Our site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are not under our control. We are not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small piece of information stored on your hard drive, that many Web sites use to help make shopping online easier. It lets you shop our site and place items in your cart and return later without having to re-enter the information. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies and also provide the option to disable this feature.

 **Security  
** Our site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. All information is stored on a secure server.

We strive to maintain the reliability, accuracy, completeness and currency of personal data in our databases and to protect the privacy and security of our databases. Although we cannot guarantee against any loss, misuse, unauthorized disclosure, alteration or destruction of data, we try to prevent such unfortunate occurrences.

 **Safe Shopping Policy  
** Because your credit card security is our highest priority, we have taken numerous steps to ensure that your payment information is processed confidentially, accurately and securely. Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) uses Secure Sockets Layer (SSL), an encryption technology that protects your credit card information. SSL encrypts all ordering information (name, address, credit card number) so no one can read it as it travels over the Internet. 

**Children's Guidelines  
** At Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/), the safety of children is very important to us. We are committed to protecting the online privacy of children. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information about children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent. If you are under 13 and would like to purchase items from Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) or provide personal information about yourself and your family, please ask a parent or guardian for assistance.

Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) cannot prohibit minors from visiting this site. Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) must rely on parents, guardians and those responsible for supervising children under the age of 13 to decide which materials are appropriate for such children to view and/or purchase.

Each time you purchase a product at Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) or provide information about yourself or your family, you are representing to Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) that you are 13 years or older.

 **Choice/Opt-Out**  
We offer you the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request the information. You may sign in to your account at Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) and alter any choices you made or information you previously supplied. You may also contact us at [Info@We-Are-Gamers.com](mailto:Info@We-Are-Gamers.com).

 **Correct/Update**

To correct the information you�ve provided us you can log into your account at Gamers United - [www.We-Are-Gamers.com](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) or send us an email at: [Info@We-Are-Gamers.com](mailto:Info@We-Are-Gamers.com). 

**Contacting Gamers United -**[ **www.We-Are-Gamers.com**](http://www.we-are-gamers.com/) ** **

Please contact us if you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site: 

> You can send e-mail at: 
>
